[With English subtitles]
[有英文字幕]
This is the near future.
这是不久的将来。
Gene editing technology is developing rapidly.
基因编辑技术发展迅速。
A scientific life form called a "humanoid"
一种被称为“类人生物”的科学生命体
has been created.
已经被创造了。
Physiological Structure of Humanoids
类人生物的生理结构
Almost the same as humans.
与人类几乎相同。
the only difference
唯一的区别
are the neurons in their brains
是他们大脑中的神经元
Gene editing has been done in some way.
已经以某种方式进行了基因编辑。
They have a single original obsession that they must abide by.
他们有一个必须遵守的唯一最初的执念。
They can be loyal spouses until the end of their lives.
他们可以成为忠诚的配偶， 直到生命的尽头。
They can be docile and filial children.
他们可以是温顺孝顺的孩子。
They can become employees who are loyal to their bosses.
他们可以成为忠于老板的员工。
These custom-made humanoids begin circulating
这些定制的人形生物开始流通
as a commodity on a global scale.
作为全球范围内的商品。
Even in some producing countries
即使在一些生产国
Selling humanoid robots is illegal,
销售人形机器人是非法的，
There are still lawless people
仍有不法之徒
who brought
谁带来
Humanoids entering their country without permission
类人生物未经许可进入他们的国家
and sell them secretly.
并秘密出售它们。
With the widespread spread of humanoid creatures,
随着类人生物的广泛传播，
Their risks gradually became apparent.
他们的风险逐渐显现。
more and more people
越来越多人
Become addicted to
开始沉迷于
Fake emotions provided by humanoids.
类人生物提供的虚假情感。
As for the humanoids themselves,
而对于类人生物本身来说，
their thoughts and emotions
他们的想法和情感
easily transformed
容易变形
Within the limits of initial obsession.
在最初的执念的限制下。
Many vicious events occurred as a result.
由此发生了许多恶性事件。
Facing the increasingly severe situation,
面对 越来越严峻的形势，
The international community quickly convened a meeting.
国际社会 迅速召开会议。
Humanoid robot production bans and recalls
人形机器人的生产禁令 和召回
Passed unanimously.
获得一致通过。
According to the agreement,
根据协议，
All countries will immediately stop producing humanoid robots.
所有国家将立即停止生产人形机器人。
They should also recall and centralize management
他们还应该召回并集中管理
All humanoids in their country.
他们国家的所有类人生物。
Xin Genomics Institute
辛基因组研究所
It was soon established in Xiyuan City.
很快就在西苑市成立了。
It's to cooperate with the police
是为了配合警方
Find and identify our country's humanoid creatures.
寻找并识别 我国的类人生物。
However, the process was not smooth.
然而，这个过程并不顺利。
The only way to identify humanoids
识别人形生物的唯一方法
Just inject identification drugs
就是注射识别药物
Then observe whether the pupils change color.
然后观察瞳孔是否会变色。
But there are still flaws in identifying drugs.
但鉴定药物仍有缺陷。
It is very harmful to ordinary people.
对于普通人来说危害很大。
Therefore, its use is strictly restricted.
因此，其使用受到严格限制。
Until now,
到现在为止，
five years have passed
五年过去了
After the humanoid ban was enacted.
人形禁令颁布后。
There are still some humanoids
仍然有一些人形生物
[bionic life]
[仿生生命]
living among us.
生活在我们中间。
[episode 1]
[第1集]
[Xin Genomics Institute]
[辛基因组研究所]
[Investigation Group Three]
【调查三组】
Sorry I'm late.
不好意思我迟到了。
What's happening here?
这是什么情况？
Let's start.
让我们开始。
deceased
死者
Is a woman.
是一名女性。
Three days ago,
三天前，
She broke into a spa hotel armed with weapons.
她携带武器闯入一家温泉酒店。
She ended up injuring a mother and her son in the room.
她最终在房间里打伤了一位母亲和她的儿子。
[The monster wields a knife late at night, and a 10-year-old boy risks his life to save his mother]
【妖孽深夜挥刀，10岁男孩冒生命危险救母亲】
In order to protect my mother,
为了保护母亲，
The kid stabbed the mad woman to death.
那孩子把疯女人刺死了。
She fell into the fire pit
她掉进了火坑
Her face was burned.
她的脸被烧伤了。
The body was severely burned,
尸体被严重烧伤，
So it cannot be identified.
所以无法识别。
The deceased was unidentified.
死者身份不明。
And it doesn't match files that have been lost over the past few months.
而且它与过去几个月丢失的文件不匹配。
So the police need our cooperation
所以警方需要我们的合作
Go through the identification process
进行身份识别过程
Check to see if she is a humanoid.
检查她是否是人形生物。
Her body was severely burned
她的身体被严重烧伤
You can't even see her pupils.
甚至看不到她的瞳孔。
Of course, medicine doesn't work either.
当然，药物也不起作用。
Our job will be difficult.
我们的工作将会很困难。
Even if she is in human form,
就算她是人形，
She is dead.
她已经死了。
The Sheen Genome Institute does not need to be involved.
Sheen 基因组研究所不需要参与其中。
Right, Cheng Nuo?
Right, Cheng Nuo?
What's the expression on this kid's face?
这孩子脸上是什么表情？
Didn't he just kill someone?
他不是刚刚杀了人吗？
No matter how mature he is,
无论他多么成熟，
He shouldn't be so calm.
他不应该这么冷静。
let's go.
我们走吧。
We will take over the case.
我们会接手这个案子。
Because of thunderstorm weather,
因为雷雨天气，
Surveillance camera signals are affected,
监控摄像头信号受到影响，
So they were on and off.
所以他们时断时续。
I heard a loud noise
我听到很大的噪音
from upstairs.
从楼上。
I checked the CCTV and something felt wrong.
我查看了闭路电视，感觉有些不对劲。
Then I ran up.
然后我就跑了上去。
We will obtain a copy of the surveillance video.
我们将获取监控录像的副本。
no problem.
没问题。
Police cordoned off the room
警方封锁了房间
After they got the evidence.
他们拿到证据后。
They won't let us in for now.
他们暂时不让我们进去。
if you want to go in
如果你想进去的话
you can...
你可以...
What happened to him?
他究竟怎么了？
sorry.
对不起。
When the mother and son were taken away by the police,
当母子俩被警察带走时，
are u there?
你在吗？
I was on duty in the lobby that day.
那天我在大厅值班。
How is the child?
孩子怎么样了？
Is he scared?
他害怕了吗？
Not really.
并不真地。
The rooms on both sides were unoccupied.
两边的房间里都没有人住。
There is a couple living in room 0210.
0210室住着一对夫妇。
How long were they there?
他们在那里待了多久？
They booked the room for 7 days.
他们预订了7天的房间。
gentlemen.
先生。
You can't knock on the door like this.
你不能这样敲门。
What are you doing? Why are you knocking so loudly?
你在干什么？你为什么敲得那么大声？
Miss Wang, I'm sorry to bother you.
王小姐，抱歉打扰您了。
The two men are researchers at the Xin Genome Institute.
这两个人是辛基因组研究所的研究人员。
They have some questions to ask.
他们有一些问题要问。
Aren't you done yet?
你还没有完成吗？
You've asked this many times!
你已经问了很多次了！
Please repeat.
请再重复一遍。
I'm telling you for the last time.
我最后一次告诉你。
That day,
那天，
I heard someone walking back and forth
我听到有人来回走动
in the corridor.
在走廊里。
then i heard someone
然后我听到有人
Knock on every door.
敲每一扇门。
after that,
在那之后，
I heard a loud noise.
我听到一声巨响。
I pushed my boyfriend at that time.
我当时就推了我男朋友。
He was sound asleep.
他睡得很熟。
Did she knock on your door too?
她也敲过你的门吗？
Yes.
是的。
I walked near the door
我走到门附近
and scolded her.
并骂了她。
I thought some drunkard was drunk
我以为某个酒鬼喝醉了
And went to the wrong door.
并走错门了。
But nothing happened after that.
但此后什么也没发生。
wait.
等待。
you mean
你的意思是
She left when she heard your voice?
她听到你的声音就走了？
Yes.
是的。
Thinking about it now, I'm really scared.
现在想起来，我真的很害怕。
- she must be looking - by the way
-她一定是在找 -顺便说一句
-Some specific goals. -when will you
-一些具体目标。 -你什么时候
Give me mental compensation?
给我精神赔偿？
If you don't leave I won't leave.
如果你不离开我就不会离开。
Did you hear anything else?
你还听到别的什么吗？
after that i heard
之后，我听到
Very loud noise.
非常大的噪音。
I also heard a woman scream,
我还听到一个女人的尖叫声，
“Let go of my child.
“放开我的孩子。
Let go of my child! "
放开我的孩子！”
Since you and the people from Xin Genomics Institute are here,
既然你们，辛基因组研究所的人都在这里，
Is that crazy woman in human form?
那个疯女人是人形吗？
——He must have killed that person ——Cheng Nuo.
——他肯定杀了那个人 ——程诺。
To save his mother.
为了救他的母亲。
Stop making wild guesses.
别再胡乱猜测了。
Thanks.
谢谢。
You have come a long way to get here.
你千里迢迢来到这里。
here.
这里。
But I don't think I can help you
但我不认为我能帮助你
with what you asked.
与你所问的。
we just doubt
我们只是怀疑
The person who attacked you that day
那天袭击你的人
Possibly a humanoid.
可能是一个人形生物。
Humanoid?
人形生物？
I have no idea.
我不知道。
I am really scared.
我好害怕。
I've told you all I can remember.
我已经把我能记得的都说了。
Ms. Chen,
陈女士，
Where is your son?
你的儿子在哪里？
We want to see him.
我们想见他。
sorry.
对不起。
He is sleeping.
他在睡觉。
It was not easy for him to fall asleep.
他要睡着并不容易。
Do you want to talk to him?
你想和他说话吗？
I know everything he knows.
我知道他所知道的一切。
Can I tell you?
我可以告诉你吗？
certainly.
当然。
can you tell us
你能告诉我们吗
What happened when you were attacked the day before yesterday?
前天你被袭击时发生了什么？
Yuan won second place in the piano competition.
袁在钢琴比赛中获得第二名。
I agreed
我答应了
Take him to a hot spring hotel to stay for two days.
带他去温泉酒店住两天。
Did you have fun today?
今天你玩得开心吗？
Yes.
是的。
Have sweet dreams.
做个好梦。
who is it?
是谁？
Let go of my child.
放开我的孩子。
Let go of my child!
放开我的孩子！
Yuan, run!
元，快跑！
This is what happened.
这就是发生的事情。
Who do you think she is?
你以为她是谁？
Why did she attack you?
她为什么攻击你？
tramp?
流浪汉？
or
或者
People in mental hospitals?
精神病院里的人？
A humanoid, as we suspected?
正如我们怀疑的那样，是一个人形生物？
But it doesn't matter.
但没关系。
If she were in human form
如果她是人形的话
It will be easier for us to deal with her.
我们对付她就更容易了。
Ms. Chen,
陈女士，
you know
你知道
What do we do, right?
我们做什么，对吧？
Xin Genome Institute.
辛基因组研究所。
You specialize in humanoids.
你专门研究类人生物。
then you should know
那么你应该知道
The dangers of humanoids, right?
类人生物的危险，对吗？
Ms. Chen,
陈女士，
Is there anything else you want to tell us?
您还有什么要告诉我们的吗？
You'd better do it now.
你最好现在就做。
I have nothing more to say.
我没什么可说的了。
sorry.
对不起。
I need to cook for my kids.
我需要为我的孩子做饭。
[Please trust humans again] [We will take you home]
[请再次相信人类] [我们会带你回家]
Let go of my child.
放开我的孩子。
Let go of my child!
放开我的孩子！
Hello.
你好。
We are researchers at the Xin Genome Institute.
我们是辛基因组研究所的研究人员。
We would like to ask Fang Yuan some questions.
我们想问方源一些问题。
I need to check with his parents.
我需要和他的父母确认一下。
Please wait.
请稍候。
Cheng Nuo.
Cheng Nuo.
Fang Yuan.
Fang Yuan.
We are researchers at the Xin Genome Institute.
我们是辛基因组研究所的研究人员。
No introduction is needed to us.
无需向我们介绍。
We've met before.
我们以前见过面。
correct?
正确的？
Let me show you something.
让我给你看一些东西。
Take a look.
看一看。
Do you know this deceased person?
你认识这个死者吗？
can you speak?
你能说话吗？
Hey.
嘿。
Why are you completely unresponsive?
为什么你完全没有反应？
Cheng Nuo.
Cheng Nuo.
what are you doing here?
你在这里做什么？
How could you break in here?
你怎么能闯入这里？
What are you going to do to him?
你要对他做什么？
I just asked him a few questions.
我只是问了他几个问题。
about what?
关于什么？
My son's actions were self-defense.
我儿子的行为属于正当防卫。
He didn't do anything wrong.
他没有做错任何事。
Stop pestering him.
别再纠缠他了。
We will cooperate with the police to find out the truth
我们将配合警方查明真相
If your son's actions were legitimate self-defense.
如果你儿子的行为是合法的自卫。
Please leave.
请离开。
Has he always been so silent?
他一直都是这样沉默的吗？
go out!
出去！
Cheng Nuo, let’s go.
程诺，我们走吧。
Cheng Nuo.
Cheng Nuo.
sorry.
对不起。
Do you think it's normal for him to be like this?
你觉得他这样正常吗？
he didn't say anything
他什么也没说
Has he since that incident?
自从那次事件之后，他有吗？
You just scared him.
你刚才吓到他了。
He's just a kid.
他只是个孩子。
He just wanted to protect his mother.
他只是想保护他的母亲。
How can you say he is a murderer?
你怎么能说他是杀人犯呢？
This is not what we need to confirm
这不是我们需要确认的
What if the victim is a humanoid?
如果受害者是人形生物？
Why do you keep pestering your children?
为什么老是缠着孩子？
Dead people cannot speak.
死人不会说话。
They said they did not know the attacker.
他们说他们不认识袭击者。
Chen Xinhui said so.
陈新辉如此说道。
Fang Yuan hasn't spoken yet.
方源还没有说话。
does it matter?
有关系吗？
Yes.
是的。
Is it possible to solve a crime only by injuring someone?
难道只有伤人才能破案吗？
Then you can try your method.
那你可以试试你的方法。
Fang Yuan,
Fang Yuan,
I will protect you.
我会保护你。
Mom is here,
有妈妈在，
You don't need to worry about anything.
您无需担心任何事情。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
[Hualan Psychological Clinic]
[华蓝心理诊所]
You did very well today.
你今天表现很好。
Make sure you eat well at home.
确保你在家吃得好。
OK
好的。
he is still there
他还在
Called our nanny every day.
每天给我们的保姆打电话。
I see. This is just a process.
我明白。这只是一个过程。
You should spend more time with him.
你应该花更多的时间和他在一起。
Don't put too much pressure on him.
不要给他太大的压力。
OK, thanks.
好的谢谢。
goodbye.
再见。
Advanced.
高级的。
An Qiu.
An Qiu.
sorry.
对不起。
This time I came in a hurry,
这次我来得匆忙，
So I didn't tell you in advance.
所以我没有提前告诉你。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
I won’t beat around the bush.
我不会拐弯抹角。
Here's the thing.
事情是这样的。
I know
我知道
you are good at
你擅长
psychological problems.
心理问题。
We happen to have a case
我们正好有一个案例
We would like to ask you to help us.
我们想请您帮助我们。
Is it about humanoids?
是关于人形生物的吗？
Yes and no.
是和不是。
We're not sure yet.
我们还不确定。
Those involved have refused to speak.
涉案人员一直拒绝说话。
So I want you to take a look.
所以我想让你看一下。
-Multiple sclerosis. Zhang. -I want to see my husband.
-多发性硬化症。张. -我想见我的丈夫。
Miss Zhang, don't run!
张小姐，别跑！
He is not a humanoid. He is not!
他不是人形生物。他不是！
You go back first.
你先回去吧。
Let me go!
让我走！
It's okay, Miss Zhang.
没关系，张小姐。
I have a lot of people here who need help.
我这里有很多人需要帮助。
sorry.
对不起。
I see.
我明白。
but
但
This case is a bit special.
这个案例有点特殊。
The person involved was a ten-year-old child.
涉事的 是一名十岁的孩子。
he killed someone
他杀了人
To protect his mother.
为了保护他的母亲。
Advanced.
高级的。
An Qiu.
An Qiu.
They're already inside.
他们已经在里面了。
Let me take you inside.
让我带你进去。
OK
好的。
Ms. Chen.
陈女士。
Sit here.
在这里坐。
sorry.
对不起。
My colleague was too impulsive last time.
上次同事太冲动了。
But don't worry.
但不用担心。
We will not discuss the case this time.
这次我们不讨论这个案子。
we are worried
我们很担心
After experiencing these things
经历了这些事情之后
Fang Yuan was under too much mental pressure.
方源精神压力太大了。
So I specially invited
所以特地邀请了
Psychology expert.
心理学专家。
Hope she can help Fang Yuan.
希望她能够帮助方源。
Hello, Ms. Chen.
陈小姐，您好。
My name is An Qiu.
我叫安秋。
Can I chat with Fang Yuan?
我可以和方源聊天吗？
Hello, Fang Yuan.
Hello, Fang Yuan.
Can I chat with you?
我可以和你聊天吗？
if you don't say no
如果你不说不
Can I assume this is a yes?
我可以认为这是肯定的吗？
Fang Yuan.
Fang Yuan.
In fact, compared with this case,
其实与这个案例相比，
We care more about you.
我们更关心你。
but if you remain silent
但如果你保持沉默
We don't know how to help you.
我们不知道如何帮助你。
It's okay, Fang Yuan.
没关系，方源。
I totally understand how you feel.
我完全理解你的感受。
how about this?
这个怎么样？
Let's play a little game.
我们来玩一个小游戏吧。
We don’t need to talk in this game.
这场比赛我们不需要说话。
do you know?
你知道吗？
I became a psychologist
我成为一名心理学家
Because I have the power of the mind.
因为我有心灵的力量。
I have telepathy.
我有心灵感应。
Do you want to try it?
你想尝试一下吗？
Let me play with you first.
我先陪你玩吧。
certainly.
当然。
The game is very simple.
游戏非常简单。
This game is called Black Magic.
这个游戏叫做黑魔法。
Ms. Chen,
陈女士，
Please point out any position of Fang Yuan
请指出方源的任何立场
For Mr. Shen.
为沉先生。
and then,
进而，
I'll tell you the answer
我来告诉你答案
Use my telepathic powers.
使用我的心灵感应能力。
let's start.
让我们开始吧。
Ms. Chen, you are ready to begin.
陈女士，您可以开始了。
OK
好的。
Did you finish it?
你做完了吗？
Yes.
是的。
Please cooperate with Mr. Shen.
请沉先生配合。
no problem.
没问题。
Is this this place?
这是这个地方吗
Ms. Chen pointed?
陈女士指着？
No.
不。
is it here?
是这里吗？
Then...
然后...
Yes.
是的。
Do you doubt it?
你怀疑吗
Mr. Shen gave me some tips?
沉先生给了我一些提示？
You must have discussed it beforehand
你们一定事先讨论过
and agree that the fifth is the correct answer.
并同意第五个是正确答案。
It's not like that.
不像那样。
Do you use your eyes to communicate?
你用眼睛来交流吗？
Not really.
并不真地。
how about this?
这个怎么样？
Let's play it again.
我们再玩一次吧。
Think about your favorite dessert
想想你最喜欢的甜点
And only told Mr. Shen.
并只告诉沉先生。
I won't look at you this time either.
这次我也不会看你了。
hurry up.
快点。
Almond jelly.
杏仁果冻。
Fang Yuan’s favorite dessert? ? ?
方媛最喜欢吃甜品？？？
ice cream?
冰淇淋？
No.
不。
Yeah
是吗
Black forest cake?
黑森林蛋糕？
No.
不。
Is it almond jelly?
是杏仁果冻吗？
Yes.
是的。
Do you believe me now?
现在你相信我了吗？
Actually,
实际上，
In addition to telepathy,
除了心灵感应之外，
I have another mental strength.
我还有另一种精神力量。
I can read your mind.
我能读懂你的心思。
Do you want to try it?
你想尝试一下吗？
I'm hungry.
我饿了。
I want to eat.
我想吃东西。
Didn't you have breakfast before coming?
你来之前没吃早饭吗？
I want to eat more.
我想吃更多。
Okay, I'll buy you something to eat.
好的，我去给你买点吃的。
Stay here and be a good person.
留在这里，做个好人。
Do you want to continue?
你想继续吗？
Actually you still want it
其实你还是想要
Watch my telepathy.
观看我的心灵感应。
Actually,
实际上，
You don't want to eat it at all.
你根本不想吃。
You just made an excuse
你只是找了个借口
Let her go.
让她离开。
you don't want her
你不想要她
Listen to your thoughts.
听听您的想法。
She takes good care of you.
她把你照顾得很好。
But does it also stress you out?
但这也让你感到压力？
but you are
但你是
He is a very sensible child.
是一个非常懂事的孩子。
Are you willing to understand your mother?
你愿意理解你的妈妈，
correct?
正确的？
My mother used to be very busy at work.
我妈妈以前工作很忙。
She barely had time for me.
她几乎没有时间陪我。
I don't blame her.
我不怪她。
But she actually wants to spend more time with you.
但她实际上想花更多的时间和你在一起。
That's why she took you to the hot spring hotel.
所以她才带你去温泉酒店。
but
但
what happened that day
那天发生了什么
Make you sad all the time.
让你一直难过。
correct?
正确的？
Yuan.
元。
you are very brave.
你很勇敢。
You did nothing wrong.
你没有做错什么。
You protected your mother.
你保护了你的母亲。
so...
所以...
Is protecting mom the most important thing?
保护妈妈是最重要的吗？
certainly.
当然。
You did cheat.
你确实作弊了。
I have no idea
我不知道
how did you do it,
你是怎么做到的，
But you're not telepathic at all.
但你根本没有心灵感应。
You are here to cheat with him.
你是来和他一起欺骗的。
Yuan.
元。
Can you tell me
你能告诉我吗
What about this pocket watch?
关于这款怀表？
Yuan, what's wrong?
袁，怎么了？
Sorry, Miss Chen.
对不起，陈小姐。
Just now, he might...
刚才，他或许……
Yuan.
元。
We go home.
我们回家吧。
Ms. Chen.
陈女士。
let's go.
我们走吧。
Sorry, I can't be of much help.
抱歉，我帮不了什么忙。
Your arrival is such a big help.
你的到来真是一个很大的帮助。
I think Fang Yuan does have something to say.
我觉得方源确实有话要说。
But maybe he has some concerns.
但也许他有一些担忧。
On the contrary, I think
相反，我认为
Chen Xinhui's reaction was a little strange.
陈新辉的反应有些奇怪。
Did your fingers touch him?
是你的手指触碰过他吗？
what are you saying?
你在说什么？
The game you just played.
你刚刚玩的游戏。
Or maybe it's a physical cue.
或者这是一种物理暗示。
This is my partner Cheng Nuo.
这是我的搭档程诺。
This is my junior An Qiu.
这是我的大三学生安秋。
She is a top student majoring in psychology.
她是心理学专业的尖子生。
Hello.
你好。
Or something you discussed
或者是你们讨论过的
before you go in.
在你进去之前。
The answer is predetermined.
答案是预先确定的。
Stop guessing. They are all wrong.
别再猜测了。他们都错了。
Incorrect?
错误的？
So what is this?
那这是什么？
Didn't you see all this?
你没看到这一切吗
Were you in the control room just now?
刚才在监控室里？
You still don't understand?
你还是不明白吗？
this is actually a game
这实际上是一个游戏
We play a lot in therapy.
我们在进行心理治疗时经常玩耍。
The principle is simple.
原理很简单。
Just make a mark? ? ?
就做个记号？？？
I knew it.
我就知道。
You must have marked your answer.
您一定已经在答案上做了标记。
correct?
正确的？
of course not.
当然不是。
The answer is always different.
答案总是不同的。
if this were not the case
如果不是这样的话
So where do you mark it?
那你在哪里标记呢？
Think about it.
想一想。
I'll see her off.
我来送她。
I have other things to do.
我还有别的事要做。
What comes before the answer?
答案之前是什么？
Think about it.
想一想。
Still thinking about the answer?
还在思考答案吗？
Do you really think I'm stupid?
你真觉得我傻吗？
options before correct answer
正确答案前的选项
It's something black.
是黑色的东西。
This game is called Dark Magic, right?
这个游戏叫黑魔法吧？
Are you doubting Chen Xinhui?
你是在怀疑陈新辉吗？
[Chen Xinhui, Chairman of Yige Xinyuan Clothing Co., Ltd.]
[Chen Xinhui, Chairman of Yige Xinyuan Clothing Co., Ltd.]
[Occupation: Entrepreneur]
【职业：企业家】
Yes.
是的。
Do you remember the surveillance video?
你还记得监控录像吗？
That crazy woman knocked on a lot of doors.
那个疯女人敲了很多门。
Why is only Chen Xinhui opening the door?
为什么只有陈新辉开门？
I do not think so
我不认为
they have no relationship
他们没有关系
As Chen Xinhui said.
正如陈新辉所言。
look.
看。
This is Chen Xinhui’s call record this year.
这是陈新辉今年的通话记录。
In addition to Fang Yuan’s teachers,
除了方源的老师之外，
She had almost no contact with anyone else.
她几乎没有和其他人联系过。
perhaps
或许
She only focuses on
她只专注
On her children?
在她的孩子身上？
look.
看。
So does she go out often?
那么她经常出去吗？
Does not match previous information.
与之前的信息不符。
Indeed.
确实如此。
Indeed, she goes out a lot.
确实，她经常出去。
It's also true that she doesn't like leaving home.
她不喜欢离开家也是事实。
Chen Xinhui and husband
陈新慧与丈夫
Once ran a clothing trading company.
曾经经营一家服装贸易公司。
After her husband died of illness,
丈夫因病去世后，
She is the only one who can manage it all.
她是唯一能管理这一切的人。
The profit is still quite good.
利润还是相当不错的。
However, three years ago,
然而，三年前，
She suddenly sold the company.
她突然卖掉了公司。
She never started a business again
她没有再创业
Or work from then on.
或从那时起工作。
She stayed at home.
她留在家里。
certainly,
当然，
The money she earned before
她之前赚的钱
enough to meet their daily expenses.
足以满足他们的日常开支。
so,
所以，
She suddenly changed her personality
她突然改变了性格
three years ago.
三年前。
Yuan.
元。
here.
这里。
Would you like some fruit?
吃点水果好吗？
Can I squeeze some juice for you?
我给你榨果汁好不好？
Have you been in contact with Chen Xinhui recently?
你最近和陈新辉有联系吗？
Some time ago she suddenly asked me to borrow money.
前段时间她突然向我借钱，
But I don't have that much money.
但我没有那么多钱。
She just gets mad at me.
她只是向我发脾气。
Miss Chen?
陈小姐？
She hasn't been here for a long time.
她已经很久没有来这里了。
in the past,
在过去，
She often comes here to have dinner with her colleagues.
她经常来这里和她的同事一起吃饭。
She hasn't finished speaking yet
她还没说完
The wine she keeps here
她在这里保存的酒
and the balance of the membership card.
以及会员卡的余额。
How long has it been since you last contacted Chen Xinhui?
你有多久没有和陈新辉联系了？
some years.
一些年。
So she didn't go back to your hometown
所以她没有回你的家乡
When did your father die?
你父亲什么时候去世的？
No, she didn't.
不，她没有。
Please don't mention these things again, okay?
这些事情不要再提了好吗？
They are all in the past.
他们都已成为过去。
I heard from our friends
我从我们的朋友那里听说
she sold the company
她卖掉了公司
and scolded her partner.
并责骂她的伴侣。
Did you visit her at her home?
你去她家拜访过她吗？
Yes.
是的。
It seems like someone lives there,
好像有人住在那里，
but
但
She didn't open the door when I went there.
我去那里时她没有开门。
We haven't been in contact since.
从那以后我们就没有再联系了。
In about three years,
大约三年的时间里，
Not only did she sell the company;
她不仅卖掉了公司，
But it also fell out
但也掉了出来
With all relatives and friends.
与所有的亲戚和朋友。
She had various reasons for falling out with them.
她有各种各样的理由与他们闹翻。
She borrowed money from a friend.
她向朋友借了钱。
This is understandable.
这是可以理解的。
But her brother said
但她哥哥却说
When her father died,
当她父亲去世时，
She didn't even attend the funeral.
她甚至没有参加葬礼。
This doesn't make sense.
这没有道理。
Maybe she has a secret that she doesn't want others to know.
也许她有一个不想让别人知道的秘密。
Cheng Nuo,
Cheng Nuo,
This is the autopsy result that Director Wan asked me to give you.
这是万主任让我给你的尸检结果。
I knew it.
我就知道。
What's this?
这是什么？
This is the autopsy report of the deceased.
这是死者的尸检报告。
come over.
过来。
【Evaluation Report】
【评估报告】
[An autopsy showed that the spleen was ruptured and lost due to a stab wound to the abdomen? ? ? 】
【尸检显示，腹部被刺伤导致脾脏破裂丢失？？？】
[Smoke residue was found in the lungs, indicating that a large amount of smoke was inhaled before death]
【肺部发现烟雾残留，显示死前吸入大量烟雾】
According to the autopsy report,
根据尸检报告，
The deceased had been taking hallucinogenic drugs for a long time
死者长期服用致幻药物
[Blood test showed that the deceased had been taking hallucinogenic drugs for a long time]
【验血显示死者长期服用致幻药物】
[The deceased had symptoms of muscle atrophy and malnutrition]
【死者有肌肉萎缩、营养不良症状】
and suffering from malnutrition
并患有营养不良
and muscle atrophy before death.
以及死前的肌肉萎缩。
She was most likely imprisoned.
她很可能被监禁了。
do you remember
你是否记得
What did Ms. Wang at the hotel say?
酒店的王小姐怎么说？
Then I heard a loud noise.
然后我听到很大的声音。
She said she heard someone screaming
她说她听到有人尖叫
“Let go of my child.
“放开我的孩子。
Let go of my child! "
放开我的孩子！”
If we take it literally,
如果我们从字面上理解的话，
we subconsciously believe
我们潜意识地相信
Chen Xinhui said so.
陈新辉这么说道。
But I listened carefully to the recording
但我仔细听了录音
And found that something was wrong with the tone.
并发现 语气有些不对劲。
Let go of my child.
放开我的孩子。
Let go of my child!
放开我的孩子！
She emphasizes "my"
她强调“我的”
Rather than "let go".
而不是“放手”。
So I think
所以我认为
It should be the crazy woman who said this.
说这话的应该是那个疯女人吧。
This is the real Chen Xinhui.
这才是真正的陈新辉。
Well, it's clear now.
好吧，现在很清楚了。
signature.
签字。
Cheng Nuo,
Cheng Nuo,
we shouldn't
我们不应该
Should I be more cautious before signing?
签字之前要更加谨慎吗？
Fang Yuan is still just a child.
方源还只是个孩子。
If we took away his only family
如果我们带走他唯一的家人
I'm afraid he can't bear such a huge blow.
恐怕他无法 承受如此巨大的打击。
-And, Chen Xinhui... -Are you speaking for humanoids?
-而且，陈新辉... - 你是在为人形生物说话吗？
have you ever thought about
你有没有想过
What does this result mean to them?
这个结果对他们意味着什么？
That's not what I should be thinking about.
那不是我应该考虑的。
Neither do you.
你也没有。
You just need to judge
你只需要判断
If the target is a humanoid. that's all.
如果目标是人形生物。就这样。
so,
所以，
Is protecting mom the most important thing?
保护妈妈是最重要的吗？
certainly.
当然。
You did cheat.
你确实作弊了。
I don't know how...
我不知道怎么...
Protect mom...
保护妈妈...
[Is protecting mother the most important thing? 】
【保护妈妈是最重要的吗？】
Hello, senior.
你好，前辈。
I want to leave the Xin Genome Institute.
我想离开辛基因组研究所。
Why?
为什么？
You still remember my partner Cheng Nuo, right?
你还记得我的搭档程诺吧？
The difference between humanoids and humans
类人生物与人类的区别
Just the initial obsession.
只是最初的痴迷。
It is the basis of all behavior
它是一切行为的基础
and humanoid emotions.
和类人生物的情感。
It's like an instinct.
这就像一种本能。
Sheen Genome Institute aims to work with police
Sheen基因组研究所的目的是与警方合作
Identify and search for humanoids.
识别和搜索类人生物。
But at the same time we also need to care for them.
但同时我们也需要给予他们关怀。
However, Cheng Nuo was different.
然而程诺不同。
he has been hostile
他一直充满敌意
Towards the humanoids.
朝向类人生物。
To identify humanoids,
为了识别人形生物，
He is willing to do anything.
他愿意做一切事情。
But humanoids
但人形生物
Not a robot.
不是机器人。
They look just like us.
他们看起来和我们一样。
They could be any one of us.
他们可以是我们中的任何一个人。
Every time I look for humanoids
每次我寻找人形生物时
I met a group of people
我遇见了一群人
Who has an emotional connection to it.
谁与它有情感上的联系。
If the human form disappears
如果人形消失了
Their lives will also change completely.
他们的生活也将彻底改变。
we need to correct
我们需要纠正
People's overreliance on humanoids.
人们对类人生物的过度依赖。
But this process
但这个过程
Makes me feel stressed.
让我感到有压力。
sorry
对不起
Let you listen to my complaints.
让你听我的抱怨。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Advanced.
高级的。
Whether we're investigators or psychologists,
无论我们是调查员 还是心理学家，
The purpose of our work is to enable people
我们工作的目的是让人们
accept the truth.
接受事实。
Some people give up on themselves,
有些人放弃了自己，
But we can't give up on them.
但我们不能放弃他们。
hold onto.
坚持住。
Maybe a turnaround will come soon.
也许转机很快就会到来。
Thanks.
谢谢。
An Qiu,
An Qiu,
Actually,
实际上，
I think you are better suited for this job than me.
我认为你比我更适合这份工作。
wait.
等待。
look at this.
看这个。
【Seasonal Recruitment】
【季节性招聘】
i saw it all
我看到了这一切
When you are talking to Fang Yuan.
当你和方源说话的时候。
If you work with Cheng Nuo,
如果你和程诺一起工作，
He might become different.
他可能会变得不一样。
Really?
真的吗？
I thought there was nothing I could do to help.
我以为我帮不了什么忙。
Incidentally,
顺便一提，
what is the end result
最终结果是什么
What about Fang Yuan’s case?
方媛的案子呢？
almost finished.
快完成了。
We may have final confirmation tomorrow.
我们可能会在明天做出最终确认。
Actually, I am still quite worried about Fang Yuan.
其实，我还是挺担心方源的。
Can I take a look tomorrow?
我明天可以看一下吗？
Mr. Shen,
沉先生，
A lady is looking for you outside.
一位女士在外面找你。
OK
好的。
An Qiu.
An Qiu.
Why are the police here?
警察怎么会在这里？
Chen Xinhui is missing.
陈新辉失踪了。
what happened?
发生了什么？
Chen Xinhui
Chen Xinhui
Identified as humanoid.
被确认为人形。
Where did that figure go?
那个人形去哪儿了？
I've been asking you for almost 30 minutes.
我已经问你差不多30分钟了。
-You won't say anything, right? -team leader.
-你不会说什么，对吧？ -队长。
I found a secret door in the living room.
我在客厅里发现了一扇暗门。
Come and take a look.
快来看看吧。
OK future.
好的。未来。
Take care of Fang Yuan for me.
替我照顾方源。
OK
好的。
I knew it.
我就知道。
Yuan.
元。
will be easier
会更容易
Tell us everything.
告诉我们一切。
Let me ask you one last time.
让我最后问你一次吧。
Where is that figure?
那个人形在哪里？
at this point,
在此刻，
What are you still hiding?
你还在隐瞒什么？
Could you please stop talking to children like this?
你能不能别跟这样的孩子说话了？
Do you know what he did?
你知道他做了什么吗？
That victim was his mother.
那个受害者就是他的母亲。
We've done DNA testing
我们已经做了DNA测试
For the deceased in the hot spring hotel,
为温泉酒店的死者，
Him, and his mother.
他，还有他的母亲。
The results show
结果表明
The victim was also Chen Xinhui.
受害人也是陈新辉。
One of them must be a humanoid.
其中之一必定是人形生物。
You won't tell, will you?
你不会告诉的，是吗？
Let me help you recall the process.
让我帮你回忆一下整个过程。
I guess
我猜
Your mother is too busy at work
你妈妈工作太忙
So she customized a human figure in Lao Cai
于是她在老街定制了一个人形
Who looks exactly like her
谁长得和她一模一样
Take care of you for her.
替她照顾你。
her first obsession
她最初的痴迷
It must be good for you
一定对你很好
and obey you unconditionally.
并无条件服从你。
stop.
停止。
Your mother has high hopes for you
你妈妈对你寄予厚望
This makes you feel stressed.
这让你感到压力很大。
That is a kind of love.
那是一种爱。
But in human eyes,
但在人形眼中，
This is a disservice.
这是一种伤害。
Humanoids are no longer satisfied
人形生物不再满足
As a surrogate mother.
作为一个替代母亲。
She thought she was more qualified
她以为自己更有资格
Become your mother.
成为你的母亲。
Teacher Yuan, I'm going to work.
袁老师，我要去上班了。
- Stay at home and listen to your aunt. -But it's not easy
- 呆在家里听阿姨的话。 -但这并不容易
to replace humans.
来代替人类。
first,
首先，
This is just basic imitation.
这只是基本的模仿。
Yuan.
元。
I go to work.
我去上班。
be a good person
做个好人
Listen to your aunt at home.
在家听阿姨的话。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Humanoid placing drugs
人形放置毒品
Get into food and water every day.
每天进入食物和水中。
Gradually,
逐步地，
There is something wrong with your mother's health.
你母亲的健康出了问题。
at the same time,
同时，
She started her plan to replace her.
她开始了她的计划来取代她。
Ms. Chen, are you sure you want to sell your company?
陈女士，您确定 要出售公司吗？
In order to avoid being discovered by people familiar to Ms. Chen,
为了避免被陈女士熟悉的人发现，
She takes the initiative
她主动
Identify areas of discord between your mother and her family and friends
找出 你母亲和她的家人朋友之间的不和点
Cut ties with everyone.
与所有人断绝关系。
Can you understand me?
你能听懂我说话吗？
I'm in charge now.
我现在负责。
I can't go back.
我无法回去。
Yuan.
元。
I've fired that nanny.
我已经解雇了那个保姆。
From now on I will take care of you wholeheartedly.
从今以后我会全心全意地照顾你。
Humanoids may be afraid to kill humans.
类人生物可能不敢杀死人类。
So she kept your mother
所以她保留了你的母亲
In the basement.
在地下室。
Your mother was drugged
你妈妈被下药了
So she is sometimes awake and sometimes confused.
所以她时而清醒 ，时而迷茫。
able...
能...
Can I ask you a question?
我可以问你一个问题吗？
when? ? ?
什么时候？？？
when i left,
当我离开的时候，
Is Fang Yuan okay?
方源还好吗？
Is he happy?
他开心吗？
Did it? ? ?
做过？？？
Does he miss his mother?
他想念他的妈妈吗？
I am his mother.
我是他的妈妈。
He is happy now.
他现在很高兴。
I won't do anything to upset him.
我不会做任何让他不高兴的事。
Drink it when you are stronger.
等你身体强壮了再喝吧。
On the day of the incident, there was a thunderstorm.
事发当天，正值雷雨天气。
basement door
地下室的门
I opened it myself,
自己打开的，
The fault may be caused by a power outage.
可能是停电导致的故障。
【Hot Spring Hotel】
【温泉酒店】
Have sweet dreams.
做个好梦。
Mom, what's wrong?
妈妈，怎么了？
It doesn't matter. Let me go and see.
没关系。让我去看看。
who is it?
是谁？
You took my child away. it was all your fault!
你夺走了我的孩子。都是你的错！
Mother!
妈妈！
Let go of my child.
放开我的孩子。
Let go of my child!
放开我的孩子！
Yuan, run!
元，快跑！
You didn't kill her, did you?
你没有杀她，是吗？
This was done by humanoids.
这是人形生物干的。
I do not understand
我不明白
Why do you still insist you did it.
为什么你仍然坚持认为是你做的。
She has abandoned you
她已经抛弃你了
But you still care about her.
但你仍然关心她。
She won't abandon me.
她不会抛弃我的。
why not?
为什么不？
The initial obsession?
最初的痴迷？
Are you so sure?
你这么确定吗
Her first obsession was to take care of you?
她最初的执念是照顾你？
Maybe he is becoming another Chen Xinhui.
也许正在成为另一个陈新辉。
that's why
这就是为什么
she got rid of real people
她摆脱了真正的人
and replaced her.
并取代了她。
And you
你呢
- Just the tools she uses. -nonsense!
——只是她使用的工具。 -废话！
This was not planned.
这不是计划好的。
She didn't mean it.
她不是故意的。
Then why did you lie?
那你为什么撒谎呢？
In the end what happened?
到底发生了什么？
Cheng Nuo.
Cheng Nuo.
Yuan. Do not be afraid. Do not be sad.
元。别害怕。别伤心。
Only by knowing the truth
只有了解真相
How can we help you?
我们可以帮助你吗？
can you tell us
你能告诉我们吗
What happened that night?
那天晚上发生了什么？
Yuan.
元。
What should we do?
我们应该做什么？
I did not do it on purpose.
我不是故意的。
I don't know my mother
我不认识我妈妈
who is with me
谁和我在一起
Until that night, she was mother in human form.
直到那天晚上，她都是人形妈妈。
Sorry, Yuan.
对不起，袁。
I am too busy.
我太忙了。
I don't have time to take care of you.
我没时间照顾你。
Here's a little gift
在这里，这是一份小礼物
Congratulations on your win.
祝贺您获奖。
I have lost my mother.
我已经失去了母亲。
I just don't want to lose another one.
我只是不想再失去一个。
You asked me that day
那天你问我
If protecting mom is the most important thing.
如果保护妈妈是最重要的事情的话。
You must be blaming yourself.
你一定很自责吧。
But I'm right.
但我是对的。
Yuan, you are very brave.
袁，你很勇敢。
You just protected your other mother.
你刚刚保护了你的另一个母亲。
Another mom?
另一个妈妈？
Having said that,
话虽如此，
She left when she was needed most.
在最需要她的时候，她还是离开了。
Yuan.
元。
She won't leave for no reason.
她不会无缘无故的离开。
You know what she went to do, right?
你知道她去做什么，对吧？
Will Mom get legal status?
妈妈会获得合法身份吗？
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
she got a call
她接到一个电话
Today comes from a stranger.
今天来自一个陌生人。
he said he knew
他说他知道
Our secret.
我们的秘密。
He can help us.
他可以帮助我们。
do you know
你知道吗
Where do they meet?
他们在哪里见面？
In Forest Park.
森林公园内。
let's break up.
我们分手吧。
Chen Xinhui.
Chen Xinhui.
Advanced.
高级的。
stop! stop!
停止！停止！
Boy saves his mother
男孩救母亲的事件
There's a surprising twist.
发生了令人惊讶的转折。
[Xiyuan City Breaking News]
【西苑城爆料】
This ten-year-old boy relies too much on humanoids
这个十岁的男孩太过于依赖人形生物
He hid it from the police
他向警察隐瞒了
The humanoid creature killed his mother for his crime.
人形生物杀死了他母亲的罪行。
The patient has inhaled too much smoke,
病人吸入过多烟雾，
Causes cerebral hypoxia and ischemia.
造成脑缺氧、缺血。
He remains in a coma.
他仍处于昏迷状态。
If the coma lasts too long
如果昏迷时间太长
He may have sequelae.
他可能会有后遗症。
Why don't you save him?
你为什么不救他？
if you hadn't run away
如果你没有逃跑的话
He might not be lying here.
他可能不会躺在这里。
I ran
我跑了
Catch the suspect.
抓住嫌疑人。
Really?
真的吗？
Has the suspect been caught?
嫌疑人抓到了吗？
for you,
给你，
Catching the suspect is more important than saving people.
抓到嫌疑人比救人更重要。
correct?
正确的？
I believe Shen Li
我相信沉力
——will make the same choice. -you are wrong.
——也会做出同样的选择。 -你错了。
He will choose to save you.
他会选择拯救你。
【Seasonal Recruitment】
【季节性招聘】
Hello, is this the Human Resources Department?
你好，请问是人事部吗？
I would like to join the Sheen Genome Institute.
我想加入 Sheen 基因组研究所。